(Penny:)Nothing.
(Leonard:)Hey, what's going on with you?
(Penny:)I don't want to
talk about it.
(Leonard:)Well, hey,
come on, just tell me.
(Penny:)Fine.
(Penny:)Lately, I kind
of feel like
(Penny:)you've been taking
me for granted.
Wh-what? Where is this
coming from?
(Sheldon:)Leonard.
(Sheldon:)She might be drunk.
(Sheldon:)All she had was chips.
(Penny:)It's just, since we got married
you seem to think
you don't have to try anymore.
(Leonard:)That is ridiculous.
(Penny:)This is exactly why I didn't
want to talk about it.
(Leonard:)No, No, no, no.
Let's talk about it.
(Leonard:)I'm the one who's made
all the effort
(Leonard:)in this relationship
since day one.
(Leonard:)Please tell me
what more I could do.
(Penny:)Okay. You know what?
Maybe I'll take Amy with me
(Penny:)to the spa this weekend instead.
(Leonard:)Fine, go ahead.
(Sheldon:)Amy is free.
(Sheldon:)She had a harp lesson
on Saturday,
but it got canceled...
(Sheldon:)Boy, when you take an interest
in people,
(Sheldon:)you really uncork
a geyser of nonsense.